thekidzpage.com 2012-06-23

# Privacy at theKidzpage.com

**Privacy Statement** ** \- _Linking_  

Security | Removing/Changing Information | Children's Guidelines | Contacting the Site | Copyright Information

divaDzine and theKidzpage™ have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: **[theKidzpage™](http://www.thekidzpage.com/)**. 

Above all, we work hard to ensure that our web site is one of the safest places for children on the World Wide Web. We recognize, adhere to and applaud the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), and keep active in seeking the best in security measures, family-safe content, and personal privacy. The following is a list of practices that theKidzpage™ follows to operate safely and effectively.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

Non-membership areas of our website do not contain forms which require users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). 

Demographic and profile data is collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

This site contains advertising links to other sites. **theKidzpage™** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our online surveys request a visitor's demographic information (like their age-group). We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

The third-party advertising technology that Doubleclick uses on this Web site uses information derived from your visits to this site to target advertising within this site. In addition, Doubleclick advertisers may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on this site and other sites. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed your browser. In addition, Doubleclick uses Web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize our online advertising. Web beacons enable Doubleclick to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits this site, to learn which banner ads bring users to our Web site and to deliver more relevant advertising. To "opt-out," please click here. http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx.

We have also contracted with ValueClick to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisement 'click-throughs', and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, ValueClick may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to any party other than the Advertiser. For more information about how the information is collected and used by ValueClick, please see ValueClick's privacy policy at <http://media.valueclick.com/privacy_consumer.shtml>

back to top

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. No personal information is gathered about our visitors in the general areas of our web site, therefore non-members will have no personal information stored on our server regarding our visitors.

If a membership section is created, members over 13 years of age, and guardians of children 12 and under, will be requested to submit basic information for registration in any member area of our site (*see above). Membership data is secured in an area not accessible to the public, and our server is stored in a 24 hour security protected area.

back to top

## Children's Guidelines - Ages 12 and Under

The guidelines below are followed by **theKidzpage™**.

  1. NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent
  2. NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent
  3. NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent
  4. NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent
  5. NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity

back to top

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

You can send email to **webmaster @thekidzpage.com** (marked with "remove" in the subject line) 

back to top

## Change/Modify

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

email **webmaster @thekidzpage.com** (marked with "update" in the subject line) 

back to top

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact : 

The Web Site Manager,  **theKidzpage™** Lighthouse Cove , Ontario Canada  
(519) 6 8 2 - 1 2 5 4  **webmaster** **@ thekidzpage.com**

*Note: This website is developed in a private residential \- home office. Therefore, our physical address has not been posted here for all to see and simply "drop in". If for any valid reason, however, our physical address is required by you, we would be happy to give you the necessary information it if you contact us by email or telephone as indicated above. 

back to top

## Copyright

Although we may provide certain graphics, which _may_ be copied by our users, (i.e. The Kidz Page banners and some clip art content), materials which are _not specifically identified as available to users_ **ARE NOT** available to anyone for use without our permission. Graphical and written content on **theKidzpage™** site are original pieces of artwork and writing, developed (under copyright) by our webmaster. ©1998-2011, **theKidzpage™** and **divaDzine**.

We hope that our contribution to kids' Internet experiences is a valuable one, and that you and your family enjoy this site.

All the Best!

back to top

* * *
